双峰
第三季  第八集
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     吃冰棒懵逼脸   詹木头
火
这车上有三个追踪装置
There are three tracking devices on this car.
翻译     Silence  小酸奶
跟紧那辆货车
Get up close behind that truck.
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     没有影子   知之
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
这样应该行
That should do it.
希望你没有气我跑走了
I hope you're not sore at me for running off.
是我太蠢被抓了
It sure was stupid of me to get caught up like I did.
谢谢你把我弄出来
Thanks for getting me out of there.
你是怎么办到的
How'd you do this?
达雅告诉我发生了什么
Darya told me what happened.
我必须得把你弄出来  雷
You needed to get out, Ray.
达雅在哪
Where's Darya?
她在等我们到了一个安全的地方
She's waiting for a phone call
给她打个电话
when we get someplace safe.
我们现在去哪
Where are we going?
你可能想去那个他们叫做"农场"的地方
You'd probably like to go to that place they call "The Farm."
正合我意
That's what I was thinking.
我们正朝那里开  我...
We're heading in the right direction.I--
说说而已
just saying.
他们不会就这么让我们走掉的
They're not gonna let us just walk.
对吗
Are they?
他们肯定不出一会儿就会来找我们的
They're bound to be looking for us soon.
你有我想要的东西  雷
You have something I want, Ray.
是的
Yes, I do.
我都记住了
I got it memorized.
所有的数字
All the numbers,
全都记牢了
memorized perfectly.
但老实说  库柏先生
But honestly, Mr. Cooper,
我觉得可能要你破财了
I think it might be worth some money.
可能  是很大一笔财
Maybe... quite a lot of money.
你这么觉得吗
You think so, do you?
是的先生  我这么觉得
Yes, sir, I do.
那这样
There it is.
走右边那条小路
Take that little road up there on the right.
离开高速  雷
Let's get off this highway, Ray.
介意我在路边停一下吗
You mind if I pull over a sec?
我要小解
I gotta take a leak.
去吧
Go for it.
雷
Ray.
我要那个情报
I want that information.
什么
Yes?
看上去你已经花光了五十万
Looks like you're out half a million.
我觉得你搞错了
Well, I think you're wrong about that.
上当了吧  蠢货
Tricked ya, fucker.
菲利普
Phillip.
我是雷
It's Ray.
我觉得他已经死了
I think he's dead,
但他好像得到了某种帮助
but he's found some kind of help, so
我不是百分之百肯定
I'm not 100 percent
我...
and-I----mm...
我看见库柏身上发生了一些事
I saw something in Cooper.
可能这就是一切的关键
It may be the key to what this is all about.
我告诉他我要去哪了
And I told him where I'm going,
所以如果他来找我  我会抓住他
so if he comes after me, I'll get him there.
女士们  先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
公路之家荣幸地欢迎
the Roadhouse is proud to welcome
九寸钉乐团
the Nine Inch Nails.
*你一直挖掘着直到鲜血涌出*
*You'll dig in places Till your fingers bleed*
*你播种的地方  感染蔓延*
*Spread the infection Where you spill your seed*
*我已记不起她来这里的原因*
*I can't remember What she came here for*
*我脑中已不剩什么记忆*
*I can't remember Much of anything anymore*
*她已离去  她已离去*
*She's gone, she's gone*
*她已消失*
*She's gone away*
*她已离去  她已离去*
*She's gone, she's gone*
*她已消失不见*
*She's gone away*
*不见...*
*Away...*
*一张小嘴在体内张开*
*A little mouth Opened up inside*
*我在看着*
*Yeah, I was watching*
*她死的那天*
*On the day she died*
*舔着她的尸体直到肌肤发黑*
*We keep licking while the skin turns black*
*沿着身体切开*
*Cut along the length*
*但那种感觉再也找不回*
*But you can't get the feeling back*
*她已离去  她已离去*
*She's gone, she's gone*
*她已消失不见*
*She's gone away*
*她已离去  她已离去*
*She's gone, she's gone*
*她已消失不见*
*She's gone away*
*她已离去  她已离去*
*She's gone, she's gone*
*她已消失不见*
*She's gone away*
*她已离去  她已离去*
*She's gone, she's gone*
*她已消失不见*
*She's gone away*
*不见*
*Away...*
1945年七月十六日
新墨西哥州白沙滩
早上五点29分  山区标准时间
十
Ten...
九
nine...
八
eight...
七
seven...
六
six...
五
five...
四
four...
三
three...
二
two...
一
one.
1945年
1946年
1947年
1948年
1949年
1950年
1951年
1952年
1953年
1954年
1955年
1956年
八月五日
新墨西哥州沙漠
你喜欢那首歌吗
Did you like that song?
喜欢
Yes.
我很喜欢那首歌
I did like that song.
你看
Oh, look.
我找到了一分钱
I found a penny.
还是字朝上的
And it's head's up.
这意味着有好运
That means it's good luck.
我希望这一分钱真能带给你好运
I hope it does bring you good luck.
搞什么
What... huh?
有火吗
Got a light?
你住在...
You live in...
城里  对吧
town, don't you?
是的
Yes.
住在学校旁边吗
You live by the school?
你是怎么知道的
How did you know that?
我就是知道
I just do.
那...
So...
我还以为你要跟玛丽一起去
I thought you were going with Mary.
没有
No.
没有  我们已经结束了
No, that's over.
那你...
Are you...
为这事伤心吗
sad about that?
不
No.
好吧  那就...
Okay, that's...
挺好的  那挺好的
that's good. That's good.
-确实挺好的  -是啊
- That's--that's good. - Yeah.
真的...
It was...
很谢谢你送我回家
really nice of you to walk me home.
我很乐意
I really wanted to.
我能不能亲你一下
Do you mind if I give you a kiss?
我不...
I don't...
我不知道  我只是...
I don't know, I'm just...
求你了  就一下
Please, just... one?
那就...
Just...
回见了
I'll see you.
回见
See you.
再见
Bye.
播送中
什么事
Yes?
有火吗
Got a light?
这是水
This is the water.
这是井
And this is the well.
喝饱
Drink full
下潜
and descend.
马是眼中的纯白
The horse is the white of the eyes
和其中的黑暗
and dark within.
这是水
This is the water.
这是井
And this is the well.
喝饱
Drink full
下潜
...and descend.
马是眼中的纯白
The horse is the white of the eyes
和其中的黑暗
and dark within.
这是水
This is the water.
这是井
And this is the well.
喝饱
Drink full
下潜
and descend.
马是眼中的纯白
The horse is the white of the eyes...
和其中的黑暗
...dark within.
这是水
This is the water.
这是井
And this is the well.
喝饱  下潜
Drink full and descend.
马是眼中的纯白
The horse is the white of the eyes.
和其中的黑暗
...and dark within.
这是水
This is the water.
这是井
And this is the well.
喝饱
Drink full
下潜
and descend.
马是眼中的纯白
The horse is the white of the eyes
和其中的黑暗
and dark within.
喝饱
Drink full...
下潜
...and descend.
马是眼中的纯白
The horse is the white of the eyes
和其中的黑暗
and dark within.
这是水
This is the water.
这是...
And this is...
喝饱
Drink full
下潜
and descend.
马是眼中的
The horse is the white...
纯白
...of the eyes
和其中的黑暗
and dark within.
这是水
This is the water.
这是井
And this is the well.
喝饱
Drink full
下潜
and descend.
马是眼中的纯白
The horse is the white of the eyes
和其中的黑暗
and dark within.
这是水
This is the water.
这是井
And this is the well.
喝饱
Drink full
下潜
and descend.
马是眼中的纯白
The horse is the white of the eyes
和其中的黑暗
and dark within.
这是水
This is the water.
这是井
And this is the well.
喝饱
Drink full
下潜
and descend.
马是眼中的纯白
The horse is the white of the eyes...
和其中的黑暗
and dark within.
这是水
This is the water.
这是井
And this is the well.
喝饱
Drink full
下潜
and descend.
马是眼中的纯白
The horse is the white of the eyes
和其中的黑暗
and dark within.